kbhgames.com 2012-10-09

# Privacy - KBH Games

We get asked a lot what our policy is on the games we put up. It's really very simple. We put up games that we find fun and we don't alter them in anyway and we always try to give credit to their creators. That's really important to us. 

If you are a creator and you have a problem with anything, let us know and we will fix it immediately. If that means altering the page to give you more credit or simply taking the game down, we will immediately make this happen for you. We get so many games submitted to us that it's impossible for us to see which ones we can and cannot put up, so please, let us know if you notice a problem. 

**KABOOHOO GAMES PRIVACY POLICY**  
Kaboohoo.com is deeply committed to your privacy. The following outlines our continued support of protecting our users' privacy.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Personal information that you provide to our site will not be disclosed to any third-party sites without your consent.

**Guests**  
We do not collect any personal information on this website. However, our web server logs all visitor information and we use this for statistical purposes. 

**Members**  
Your profile information will be available to anyone who chooses to view it. Do not put sensitive personal information in your profile. We will not share your e-mail address with anyone. It will be used to send you site news and newsletters. You may opt-out of these at any time once you've logged into the site. 

**EXTERNAL LINKS**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. 

**ADVERTISMENT**  
We pledge that we'll never have pop up on kbhgames.com. We understand how annoying they are.

**CONTACT US**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement, don't hesitate to contact us using the [contact form](http://kbhgames.com/contact/)
